<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Articles on Emily Kate</title><link>https://emilykate070.github.io/blog/articles/</link><description>Recent content in Articles on Emily Kate</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-gb</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://emilykate070.github.io/blog/articles/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>A New Shape for YA Fiction: Dean Atta's The Black Flamingo</title><link>https://emilykate070.github.io/blog/articles/dean-atta-review/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://emilykate070.github.io/blog/articles/dean-atta-review/</guid><description>It wouldn&amp;rsquo;t be new or original of me to say that poetry has changed in recent years. Poetry come to be seen as capital &amp;ldquo;P&amp;rdquo; Poetry, an institution surrounded by walls of pretention and inaccessible knowledge. But poetry has no fixed address; it doesn&amp;rsquo;t (and shouldn&amp;rsquo;t) belong to a particular voice or face or place. To say so would erase the unquantifiable amount of shapes that the genre has taken over the years.</description></item><item><title>Shows by Sex Workers That Reveal a New Side to Sexuality</title><link>https://emilykate070.github.io/blog/articles/sex-work-shows/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://emilykate070.github.io/blog/articles/sex-work-shows/</guid><description>Following along the same path as my last article about books by sex workers, I want to continue talking about the importance self-representation through other forms of media. Films and TV shows offer some added benifits when it comes to self-representation; they&amp;rsquo;re fairly accessible to audiences and provide visual representation, challenging physical assumptions of what it means to be a sex worker. Podcasts have entered our daily lives in such an influential way that they provide an outlet free for many to access and in a format that allows complex content to be unpacked over an hour or so.</description></item><item><title>What I Learned from Reading Books by Sex Workers</title><link>https://emilykate070.github.io/blog/articles/sex-work-books/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Aug 2020 11:33:16 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://emilykate070.github.io/blog/articles/sex-work-books/</guid><description>Donate to the Sex Worker Mutual Aid Fund here. So you&amp;rsquo;ve seen Hustlers? Or maybe you saw Julia Roberts in Pretty Woman and thought &amp;lsquo;hm, that doesn&amp;rsquo;t seem like such a bad job?&amp;rsquo; Wherever your image of sex workers has come from, chances are it probably didn&amp;rsquo;t come from an actual sex worker. And if recent debates have taught us anything about self-representation, it&amp;rsquo;s that it matters, like really matters.</description></item></channel></rss>